

MD. Meshkat Alam Azad Executive, IT East Coast Group, BD

# **Objectives**

As a professional IT personnel, I would work for the organization with modern technical idea's. My privious work experiences and professional skills as an IT personnel will be dedicated to the organization and drive IT team as a leading Department in any situation.

# Professional Skills

Data Analysis with Jupiter/ Power BI. Selenium testing automation.

UI Design for app/web.

Google Cloud Platform.

Windows server administration.

CISCO firewall and switches.

HTML, CSS.

Node js., Autocad 2D.

Microsoft and google products.

### Certifications

Windows server 2019 administration Microsoft azure fundamentals. Basic Java programing.

#### Education

# B.sc in Computer Engineering American International University, Bangladesh.

Jan 2014-Dec-2017

CGPA:3.02

Major: Network communication
Higher secondary school certificate
Cantonment Public Collage, Rangpur,2012

Group: Science GPA:5.00

Secondary School Certificate Rangpur Zilla School, 2010

Group: Science GPA:5.00

# **Projects**

Executive Member of network infrustructure implementation in Parkesine Products limited. Executive Member of IP phone implementation in STS HQ.

School management system using JAVA and SQL.

meshkatazad@gmail.com
+8801741699282

111/D Mohakhali South Area, Dhaka

Meshkat Azad Rangon

meshkat\_rangon

#### Experience:

#### Executive, IT

#### East Coast Group Aug 2021 - Present

- Smooth operation of organizations IT infrastructure.
- Troubleshoot LAN and WAN issues.
- Management and maintain of printer and photocopy machines .
- Involved with any new installation of the company organogram.
- Vendor communication and IT purchase.
- Troubleshoot factory side IT issues remotely or by physical visit.
- Unify Access point management.

#### Executive, IT

#### DPS STS SCHOOL, DHAKA Apr 2020 -Aug 2021.

- Manage, monitor Google admin console as a general admin.
- Provide users organizational email ID and configure user with data for attendance system.
- HIKVISION DVR management.
- Train up teachers and employees with modern education system.
- Operation of organizations ERP portal as a super admin.
- Manage organizations website with WordPress CMS.
- Installing windows and Linux OS on different circumstances.
- Elastix IP PBX dashboard monitoring and configure user role for extension users.
- Respond to inquiries and assist in troubleshooting and resolving network printer photocopy machine and bar-code scanner issues.
- Network operations for LAN trouble shooting.
- Register all the computers with organization domain and apply group policy for different OU.

# System Support Engineer

Sam solutions limited Apr 2019 - Apr 2020

- Manage, monitor and install VPN systems on client end via management portal system.
- Installation and troubleshooting of Its equipment's like Mikrotik router, Network Printer Operating systems like UBUNTU, Windows-OS.
- Install, configure, IPPBX server on client end..
- Network configuration of Din star/GOIP/SKYLINE other VOIP gateways.
- Provide 2nd and 3rd level support.
- Network operations for LAN/WAN and trouble shooting.